Internship status of the student with id 2345671 is: PASS and FAIL.
Internship status of the student with id 2345672 is: PASS and FAIL.
Internship status of the student with id 2345673 is: PASS and FAIL.
Internship status of the student with id 2345674 is: PASS and FAIL.
Internship status of the student with id 2345675 is: PASS and FAIL.
Internship status of the student with id 2345676 is: PASS and FAIL.
Internship status of the student with id 2345677 is: PASS and FAIL.
Internship status of the student with id 2345678 is: FAIL and FAIL.
Internship status of the student with id 2345679 is: FAIL and FAIL.
Internship status of the student with id 2345680 is: PASS and FAIL.
Internship status of the student with id 3456712 is: FAIL and PASS.
Internship status of the student with id 3456713 is: FAIL and PASS.
Internship status of the student with id 3456714 is: FAIL and PASS.
Internship status of the student with id 3456715 is: FAIL and PASS.
Internship status of the student with id 3456716 is: FAIL and PASS.
Internship status of the student with id 3456717 is: FAIL and FAIL.
Internship status of the student with id 3456718 is: FAIL and FAIL.
Internship status of the student with id 3456719 is: FAIL and PASS.
Internship status of the student with id 3456720 is: FAIL and PASS.
Internship status of the student with id 3456721 is: FAIL and PASS.
Internship status of the student with id 4567123 is: FAIL and PASS.
Internship status of the student with id 4567124 is: FAIL and PASS.
Internship status of the student with id 4567125 is: PASS and PASS.
Internship status of the student with id 4567126 is: PASS and FAIL.
Internship status of the student with id 4567127 is: PASS and FAIL.
Internship status of the student with id 4567128 is: PASS and PASS.
Internship status of the student with id 4567129 is: PASS and PASS.
Internship status of the student with id 4567130 is: PASS and PASS.
Internship status of the student with id 4567131 is: PASS and PASS.
Internship status of the student with id 4567132 is: FAIL and PASS.
